Gene Basset Papers
Gene Basset Papers
- Cartoons, 1,319 items
  - Cartoons, 1968, Oct (Oversize 10)
    Oct 15: The Wallace-LeMay platform: George Wallace, Curtis LeMay
    Oct 16: My credentials, Senor: Panama
    Oct 17: Relax, baby...We're legal now: Czechoslovakia, Soviet Union
    Oct 18: Looks like Dick is gonna win this race too: Richard Nixon, Hubert Humphrey, George Wallace
    Oct 21: Booster shot: Jacqueline Kennedy Onassis
    Oct 22: Bunk mates: Vietnam War, Curtis LeMay, Mao Zedong, Strom Thurmond
    Oct 23: Super Eagle: space exploration
    Oct 24: Don't worry, I'll tuck you in safe from all those terrible things like integration: George Wallace
    Oct 25: You sorta learn to live with this in New York: New York City, welfare, teacher's strike, police
    Oct 26: ELECT Humphrey MUSKIE, VOTE NIXON Agnew: Richard Nixon, Hubert Humphrey
    Oct 28: Capitalist: Soviet Union, Olympics
    Oct 29: Rally round the flag, boys: George Wallace
    Oct 30: Control yourself, Hubert...I said I'd endorse, not support you: Eugene McCarthy
  - Cartoons, 1968, Nov (Oversize 10)
    Nov 1: Blockbuster?: Vietnam War, elections, Lyndon B. Johnson
    Nov 2: Every cloud must have a silver lining: Richard Nixon, Hubert Humphrey
    Nov 5: Brace yourself: elections
    Nov 6: Hail to the chief: electoral system
    Nov 7: You and your bombing policy: Curtis LeMay, George Wallace, elections
    Nov 8: I'm the new Doc but I'll need your help: Richard Nixon
    Nov 9: Let a winner lead the way: Nguyen Van Thieu, Vietnam War, peace
    Nov 11: THINK: Spiro T. Agnew, Richard Nixon
    Nov 12: Relax, we made it, didn't we?: electoral system
    Nov 13: The Charge of the Light Brigade: China, United Nations
    Nov 19: The leaning Tower of Paris: France, Charles De Gaulle, gold
    Nov 20: Step aside, buster...heah come de real judge!: Adam Clayton Powell, Supreme Court, Congress
    Nov 21: Isn't that the guy who doesn't believe in nets?: Charles De Gaulle
    Nov 22: Gentlemen, I owe it all to blood, sweat and tears: Germany, France, Britain, Harold Wilson, Charles De Gaulle, Kurt Georg Kiesinger
    Nov 23: Believe me, you got me all wrong...I'm really a dove: NATO, Soviet Union
    Nov 25: Stop gap: Charles De Gaulle, austerity program
    Nov 27: After a number of reassuring sessions my partner has agreed to attend the Peace Talks: Lyndon B. Johnson, Nguyen Van Thieu, Vietnam War
    Nov 29: Au revoir, mon ami: nuclear weapons, Charles De Gaulle
    Nov 30: Untie yourself before it's too late: Vietnam War, Richard Nixon
  - Cartoons, 1968, Dec (Oversize 10)
    Dec 2: Help: NAACP, Black Panthers, violence
  - Cartoons, 1969, Jan (Oversize 10)
    Jan 2: I said John...tell that darn donkey this is no time for a change: Russell Long, Stewart Udall, Ted Kennedy, John McCormack
    Jan 3: It says the Soviets have warned Israel about over-reaction: Czechoslovakia, press
    Jan 4: Some protection!: Ted Kennedy, Russell Long, Roman Hruska, Hugh Scott
    Jan 6: How do you like the new me?: Congress
    Jan 7: Hop aboard, Mr. President and off we go into the wild blue yonder: Vietnam War, Lyndon B. Johnson
    Jan 7: Lodge in for Harriman: Averell Harriman, Vietnam War
    Jan 8: I got something to absorb the inflation shock: Congress
    Jan 11: Actually we're only divided on direction: Vietnam War, peace
    Jan 14: Now how did I miss this loophole?: Internal Revenue Service, trucking industry
    Jan 15: Considering everything, things could be worse?: violence, Vietnam War, inflation, Lyndon B. Johnson
    Jan 16: You should be honored to carry my brand: Lyndon B. Johnson, Richard Nixon
    Jan 17: Look, comrades...it's also possible to get together on Earth: space exploration, peace talks
    Jan 18: Bail me out, part way: taxes, Congress, Lyndon B. Johnson
    Jan 18: Man, did I have a nightmare...I dreamed they gave us everything we asked for: civil rights, education
    Jan 20: Launching pad: Richard Nixon
    Jan 21: Back to Earth: Richard Nixon
    Jan 22: Say uh, Mac...which way to Austin?: Lyndon B. Johnson
    Jan 23: For your sake, Comrade, call off the dogs!: Soviet Union, Egypt, Suez Canal
    Jan 25: Well, Admiral, it's not exactly an open and shut case: USS Pueblo
    Jan 27: For propriety's sake: Alan Boyd, railroad industry
    Jan 28: Ladies and Gentlemen, as you are well aware, this set needs a new approach: Richard Nixon
    Jan 29: Testing, one, two, three....: Middle East, Iraq
    Jan 30: Gimme that ball...I'll show you how to really play this game: Everett Dirksen, Congress, professional football
    Jan 31: You'll be happy to know that the 1968 squeeze of 4.2 percent was not a record: cost of living, consumers
  - Cartoons, 1969, Feb (Oversize 10)
    Feb 1: This'll keep you out of the draft: Richard Nixon, armed forces
    Feb 4: The glutton: Congress
    Feb 5: We're right behind you, Champ: taxes
    Feb 6: Don't reach, Pardner...you're in FCC Country now: tobacco industry, advertising
    Feb 10: Launching Pad: anti-missile system
    Feb 11: Help, help!: oil
    Feb 12: See how his chin provoked my fist: elections, Germany
    Feb 13: Look, if you don't make it on your next trip, I got some newer models: Congress, electoral system
    Feb 14: And then we start demonstrating because there's no place to go to class: demonstrations
    Feb 15: And presto..a live conspiring rabbit: Jim Garrison, Clay Shaw
    Feb 19: C'mon, we're going to celebrate our victory over El-Al: Middle East
    Feb 20: Think of it...me, hooked on socialized medicine: Medicare
    Feb 21: I'm only following orders: taxes, Internal Revenue Service
    Feb 24: Only when your forces withdraw can we work out a settlement: students, demonstrations
    Feb 26: I'd like to discuss if it's necessary to sock it to me: anti-missile systems
    Feb 27: News item...Detroit: Car manufacturer recalls 4.9 million cars and trucks because of INSIDE exhaust fumes: pollution
    Feb 28: [Uncle Sam as a police officer with a young boy "South Vietnam"]: Vietnam War, Laos
    Feb 28: Wait, let us help diffuse it: college students, demonstrations
  - Cartoons, 1969, Mar (Oversize 11)
    Mar 1: Shucks, all it needs is a little tuneup: Richard Nixon, electoral system
    Mar 3: Truce with DeGaulle: Richard Nixon, Charles De Gaulle
    Mar 4: No two-bit imperialistic gangster is going to rush me around: Soviet Union, china
    Mar 6: Wanna open up some more?: Richard Nixon, Soviet Union
    Mar 8: Those daring young men without their trapeze: space exploration
    Mar 11: Refuge: Martin Luther King Jr., James Earl Ray
    Mar 12: Brinkmanship: Middle East, Israel
    Mar 13: Still growing: crime, Federal Bureau of Investigation, J. Edgar Hoover
    Mar 14: ...showing conclusively that the enemy is fighting a real guard action: Vietnam War, casualties
    Mar 15: Solomon's decision: Richard Nixon, Russia, anti-missile systems
    Mar 17: Think of it this way..you're not losing a smaller company, you're gaining a bigger one: anti-trust laws
    Mar 18: You're right...we've captured the corner: black college students, militancy
    Mar 19: Stand back...what do you think I am, a magician: Richard Nixon, Vietnam War
    Mar 20: I don't care how big you are...nobody can make sport of her majesty: Britain, Rhodesia, Harold Wilson, Ian Smith, Anguilla
    Mar 21: Getaway: organized crime
    Mar 22: Ain't she a peach: anti-missile systems, foreign policy
    Mar 25: Hold on,can't you see we're a couple of consenting adults?: anti-trust laws
    Mar 26: Nonsense a new mount…four years rest and she's as good as new: electoral system, Congress
    Mar 27: Don't worry...I'm hitting the brake: inflation, taxes, Richard Nixon
    Mar 28: I think you filled 'er up: taxes, economy
    Mar 31: Mascot: Middle East, terrorism, Hussein of Jordan
  - Cartoons, 1968, Apr (Oversize 11)
    Apr 1: The train to Abilene: Dwight Eisenhower
    Apr 2: I got a better idea...you clean it up!: oil, pollution
    Apr 3: Semi-neutral: Israel, Middle East, United Nations
    Apr 4: No more cherries on top of your desserts: Melvin R. Laird, Pentagon
    Apr 5: Is that you or he talking, Mr. President?: Melvin R. Laird, Richard Nixon, Edward Muskie, Russia
    Apr 7: Two birds with one belt: inflation, consumers
    Apr 9: Any suggestions?: Hussein of Jordan, Palestine, Richard Nixon
    Apr 10: No man's land: Vietnam War, peace
    Apr 11: Gentlemen, gentlemen...this is not Yale or Princeton: Harvard, Students for a Democratic Society, demonstrations
    Apr 12: Fort Pentagon: military budget
    Apr 14: We interrupt this program to bring you a message from our sponsor: Soviet Union, Czechoslovakia
    Apr 15: Take that and that and that: Richard Nixon, budget
    Apr 16: Howdy friend...welcome to the neighborhood: Rogers Morton, Republican Party, housing, civil rights, voting
    Apr 18: I just want to see if there is such a thing as a military industrial colossus: Melvin R. Laird
    Apr 19: Some leader...he's not even following us: Richard Nixon, North Korea
    Apr 21: I see you, too, are achieving political stability: Soviet Union, Czechoslovakia, Vietnam War, press
    Apr 22: Gentlemen, I will not tolerate the use of firearms: Cornell University, demonstrations
    Apr 23: Cigaret commercials: tobacco industry, advertising
    Apr 26: You mean this doesn't come under your crime bill?: cost of living, Richard Nixon
    Apr 28: Of all DeGaulle: France, elections, Charles De Gaulle
  - Cartoons, 1969, May (Oversize 11)
    May 3: Right behind you, buster: college students, demonstrations
    May 6: It just keeps following me: Abe Fortas
    May 7: Thank heaven, captain Bligh isn't here to see this: USS Pueblo
    May 10: Gee Ev, you can't be the manager, pitcher and batter at the same time: Everett Dirksen, Richard Nixon
    May 12: Beat it...you want to start a run on the bank?: Congress, minimum wage
    May 14: There, this'll make a new old man out of you: draft, Richard Nixon
    May 16: Now I can sleep better at night: Abe Fortas, Congress
    May 17: Decision in the balance: Richard Nixon, Supreme Court
    May 19: Hold it...I want to go over a few things: Richard Nixon, peace
    May 21: ...Tum-te-tum, into the red ink yonder...: Pentagon
    May 22: I want you to meet my choice for Chief Justice... Warren Burger: Warren Burger, law and order, Richard Nixon
    May 24: Rest assured, citizen, he's completely under control: gas and germ weapons
    May 27: Home stretch: space exploration
    May 28: We need a strong, unified and trusty political arm to to fight the Commies! Right, Fellers?: Nguyen Van Thieu
    May 30: Rocky Trip: Nelson Rockefeller, communism, Latin America, South America, Richard Nixon
    May 31: The white knight: Richard Nixon, pollution
  - Cartoons, 1968, Jun (Oversize 11)
    Jun 2: President Thieu and I are still able to see eye to eye: Nguyen Van Thieu, Richard Nixon, peace
    Jun 4: Junketing Congressmen
    Jun 5: Lucky for you I came along: Richard Nixon
    Jun 6: Where in the name of Lenin do you think you are... an SDS Convention?: communism, Students for a Democratic Society
    Jun 7: Stay calm, folks...I'll find the hang of this, yet: inflation
    Jun 9: You're not serious about removing that?: inflation, Congress, Richard Nixon
    Jun 11: Speed reading: South America
    Jun 12: Surprise!: Vietnam War, Richard Nixon
    Jun 14: Just point me in his direction...that South American is a pushover: Nelson Rockefeller, Richard Nixon
    Jun 16: We shall continue past policies with moderation: Charles De Gaulle
    Jun 17: Can't you see I have the right of way?: Supreme Court, Adam Clayton Powell, Congress
    Jun 18: ...because it's the only safe tub we got!: U.S. Navy
    Jun 19: Bye, bye, John,..try to be brave: John Lindsay, New York City, Republican Party
    Jun 20: You sure Mayor Daley isn't running this?: Students for a Democratic Society
    Jun 21: As Clifford sees Nixon and Thieu...and Nixon's version of the relationship: Nguyen Van Thieu, Richard Nixon
    Jun 23: Hold it, folks...I think I feel something, I hope: Vietnam War, peace, Richard Nixon
    Jun 24: He says it's refreshing: Nelson Rockefeller, Richard Nixon, South America
    Jun 26: Don't rush me...can't you see I'm thinking?: taxes, inflation, Congress, Richard Nixon
    Jun 27: Roll'em, Baby: movies
  - Cartoons, 1969, Jul (Oversize 11)
    Jul 1: Mother, isn't he groovy?: Soviet Union, Romania, Richard Nixon
    Jul 2: Hey, chief, you forgot something: taxes, Richard Nixon
    Jul 3: Hold it, Dick...we already have a man on that base: Richard Nixon, voting rights, civil rights
    Jul 5: Careful, Chief...you know their underhanded ways: Vietnam War, Richard Nixon
    Jul 7: Had a wonderful time...wish you were there: Latin America, Nelson Rockefeller, Richard Nixon
    Jul 9: House warming: Israel, Middle East
    Jul 10: It's our slow burn size...it lasts for years: Federal Communications Commission, tobacco industry, television industry, advertising
    Jul 12: President Thieu has my full support: Richard Nixon, Nguyen Van Thieu
    Jul 14: New arrival: Andrei Gromyko
    Jul 15: Self destruction: healthcare
    Jul 16: I think we have enough fuel for at least a liftoff: anti-missile systems, Richard Nixon
    Jul 18: Holding...: taxes
    Jul 19: No, this is not the Twilight Zone...it's a routine traffic pattern: airline industry
    Jul 23: Modification: trucking industry
    Jul 24: Tragedy - Trouble: Ted Kennedy
    Jul 28: What have they been feeding you?: space exploration
    Jul 29: [A downward moving elevator labeled "Stock Market]
  - Cartoons, 1969, Aug (Oversize 12)
    Aug 1: I think I'll go back to fish and poultry: inflation, consumers
    Aug 4: Quick, get him into quarantine: Richard Nixon, Romania
    Aug 5: Compromise: taxes, Democratic Party
  - Cartoons, 1969, Sep (Oversize 12)
    Sep 3: That's a dangerous weapon...you could blind someone!: Ted Kennedy, Edmund Dinis
    Sep 4: I have surrounded myself with men who enjoy my complete confidence: Nguyen Van Thieu
    Sep 5: Chairmanship: Ho Chi Minh
    Sep 6: Never the Comrades shall meet: Ho Chi Minh, Chou En-lai, Andrei Gromyko
    Sep 8: Why don't we take the direct route?: electoral system, Congress
    Sep 9: [director's chair marked "EV"]: Everett Dirksen
    Sep 10: AN EYE for an eye: Middle East, Israel
    Sep 11: Pandora's Box: credit
    Sep 13: Did you say no compromise till hell freezes over?: Chou En-Lai, Alexey Kosygin
    Sep 16: Bigger than ever: United Nations
    Sep 17: Entry, Entry...: Richard Nixon, Vietnam War, Nguyen Cao Ky
    Sep 18: See what Dick and Mel got for you: college students, draft (reduction)
    Sep 20: I think we ought to enforce our retirement plan: Congress, electoral system
    Sep 23: Stowaway: Congress, immigration
    Sep 24: Our hands are clean: Central Intelligence Agency, armed forces
    Sep 26: I have a good mind to sentence you to a strict ethical code!: Congress, justiciary
    Sep 27: Notice, folks, how hygienic he is this year: television industry, violence
    Sep 29: I understand we have resigned: Czechoslovakia
  - Cartoons, 1969, Oct (Oversize 12)
    Oct 1: Buckling Down: Richard Nixon, anti-war movement
    Oct 4: We're taking a pollution survey on whether to form a committee to decide whether to form a task force...: pollution
    Oct 6: Don't let it go off for 60 days, Hugh!: Hugh Scott, Vietnam War, Richard Nixon
    Oct 7: Keep shaking: Congress, armed forces
    Oct 8: I don't want you to get fully involved…maybe just another leg: Vietnam War, Laos, Nguyen Van Thieu, Souvanna Phouma
    Oct 9: The senior Senator from Massachusetts and Majority Whip feels you're not treating him like an average citizen: Ted Kennedy, press
    Oct 10: Clement and I are in this to the very end: Richard Nixon, Clement Haynsworth
    Oct 13: Peace now – Amen: peace, demonstrations, Richard Nixon
    Oct 14: We fully support this position: Clement Haynsworth
    Oct 15: A few more alterations and you'll be finished: taxes
    Oct 17: That's one small step for baseball; one giant step for the underdog: World Series
    Oct 18: I got it from reliable sources he's slowing down: inflation, Arthur Burns
    Oct 20: I await your confession, Comrade: China, Soviet Union
    Oct 22: I always wanted to be the head brewneister: Willy Brandt, Germany
    Oct 23: I have full confidence it's going to slow down: cost of living
    Oct 24: Gusher!: taxes, Russell Long
    Oct 27: Death to the infidel!: leaders of Syria, Lebanon, Egypt, Israel, United States and the Soviet Union
    Oct 28: Now to defuse this one: demonstrations, peace, Richard Nixon
    Oct 29: 50 years ago this week-40 years ago...-30 years ago...: Prohibition, stock market, World War II, inflation
    Oct 30: Pardon me, Madame Premier but your slip is showing: Golda Meir, Israel, elections
  - Cartoons, 1969, Nov (Oversize 12)
    Nov 1: Judicial Cloak: Ted Kennedy, Massachusetts
    Nov 3: Senator, are you for or undecided?: Richard Nixon, Clement Haynsworth
    Nov 4: Dammit, move, so I can get out of here!: Vietnam War, Richard Nixon
    Nov 5: Raise your right hand and place your left in the register: judiciary
    Nov 6: The non-silent majority: Richard Nixon, Virginia, New Jersey
    Nov 7: Don't worry, Judge...I have the support: Clement Haynsworth, Richard Nixon
    Nov 8: This time I won't botch it: Abdel Gamal Nasser, war
    Nov 10: The doctor says he needs more information... do it in quadruplicate: electoral system
    Nov 11: I'm just taking him out for an airing: trucking industry, drivers
    Nov 12: Now, here's my plan…: Lebanon, Middle East
    Nov 13: We stopped him again: Mao Zedong, United Nations, China
    Nov 14: Mind if I give you a boost?: peace, Vietnam War
    Nov 17: Missed him!: peace, demonstrations, militancy
    Nov 18: Peace March: nuclear weapons, Soviet Union
    Nov 19: Hey, everybody...look what I found: Vietnam War, black market
    Nov 21: Our man says he ain't coming out for round 46: Vietnam War, Richard Nixon, Henry Cabot Lodge, Jr.
    Nov 24: "...and Agnew lands a right, another right, and another right!: press, Spiro T. Agnew
    Nov 25: You see, Comrade, anything is possible: nuclear weapons, Soviet Union
    Nov 26: My boy, it's time you learned to make your own way in the world: Richard Nixon, Nguyen Van Thieu
    Nov 27: Thanksgiving: press, Spiro T. Agnew
    Nov 29: Credit us with another heroic victory in our Crusade: Middle East, terrorism
  - Cartoons, 1969, Dec (Oversize 12)
    Dec 2: You'll have to lose some weight if you want to be carried: oil, taxes
    Dec 4: ...and in turn you remember old Santa in 1970: taxes, business
    Dec 5: What, not keep Christmas?: Congress, Richard Nixon
    Dec 6: Scram, nosey!: censorship, press, My Lai massacre, Vietnam War
    Dec 8: Interference: taxes, inflation, Richard Nixon
    Dec 9: Stop the frosting: taxes, social security, Richard Nixon
    Dec 10: And now live from the East Room at the White House: Richard Nixon, press
    Dec 12: This way you're protected against freezing to death: taxes, inflation
  - Cartoons,Vietnam, 1965; 35 (Oversize 15)
    Gift of Thom Rooke, 2016
  - Cartoons,Vietnam, 1965; 36 (Oversize 16)
  - Undated A-Q (Oversize 13)
    After you, my dear sir: Nikita Khrushchev, United Nations, Charles De Gaulle
    All you have to be is able, loyal, good, efficient, and the husband of the president's secretary: Simon McHugh, Lyndon B. Johnson
    Allow me: Britain, Hong Kong
    And now it's time for Comrade Castro to demolish the United States again: Fidel Castro
    Another heavyweight title bout: Vietnam War, Russia
    Another one of those damned spontaneous demonstrations: Soviet Union, Mao Zedong, students, Alexey Kosygin, Andrei Gromyko
    Another opening, another show: U. Thant, United Nations, Soviet Union
    Any solution in sight: Middle East, United Nations
    Any suggestions?: Lyndon B. Johnson, Dominican Republic, Organization of American States
    Are you fellers sure you got the right guy?: Hubert Humphrey, labor
    As one major power to another...: Alexey Kosygin, Charles De Gaulle
    Battle of the ages: Barry Goldwater, William Scranton
    A Beginning: nuclear weapons, peace, John F. Kennedy, Harold MacMillan, Nikita Khrushchev
    Boy, you sure can take a punch!: nuclear weapons
    “Bury me!: Canada, Nikita Khrushchev
    But officer Johnson...you promised protection!: taxes
    Bye, Bye, Birdie: Barry Goldwater, Strom Thurmond, John Stennis, Frank Lausche, Russell Long
    Call me Cinderella: India, Indira Ghandi
    Catch: poverty program
    [Censure]: Christopher Dodd
    Checks and balances: Latin America, foreign aid, J. William Fulbright
    Choice of Surgeons: taxes, economy, inflation, Lyndon B. Johnson
    Compliments of the house: Adam Clayton Powell
    Considering everything, it wasn't too bad: Christmas, Vietnam War
    Curb these and you curb life, liberty and the pursuit of happiness: gun control
    Cut taxes...Increase Spending: Lyndon B. Johnson
    Daylight: voting rights, Medicare, education
    Don't anybody make a move while I consult my Mallory Rulebook: Supreme Court, crime, police
    Don't tell me Doc, it's surgery again: Great Society, Lyndon B. Johnson
    Don't you think Charlton Heston would be a perfect me for the movies if it wasn't for all his Bible films?: Nikita Khrushchev
    An Elephant sometimes remembers: Barry Goldwater, Republican Party, women
    Empty saddle in Lyndon's corral: Democratic Party, Congress
    End of a snow job: voting rights
    Escalation: Vietnam War
    First step: Middle East
    Follow me, men...men...men...: George Wallace, Lurleen Wallace, school desegregation
    French technology: Charles De Gaulle, common market
    Gee Whiz...another inheritance: Robert F. Kennedy, Robert F. Wagner
    Gentlemen - this is our problem: Association of American Editorial Cartoonists, Lyndon B. Johnson, Mao Zedong
    Great act, Shirley baby...Don't call us, we'll call you: Shirley Chissom, California, women, Vietnam War
    Grounded: peace
    Hang in there...I'm right behind you: Asia, Vietnam War, Lyndon B. Johnson
    Have matches, will travel: Ku Klux Klan
    He's fine but his image needs fixing: National Guard
    Hello Hanoi...do you read me, Hanoi?: peace, U. Thant, Vietnam War
    Help...we're being attacked by friendly forces: War on Poverty, politics
    He's my prisoner!: sports, NCAA, Amateur Athletic Union
    Hey, d'ja hear? – they busted up a draft dodging ring back home: draft, Vietnam War
    Hi, Sweetheart...don't mind her...she's strictly my last resort:
    Howdy stranger: foreign policy, Lyndon B. Johnson, domestic affairs
    I gave you an extra 36 hours...what do you want, forever?: Lyndon B. Johnson, Ho Chi Minh
    I got tired of conforming, that's why!: Vietnam War, demonstrations
    I see another long detour in your future: Great Society, anti-missile systems, Lyndon B. Johnson
    I think we've created a reasonably finished product: Congress, gun control
    I was nourished better: Soviet Union, technology, freedom
    If you don't use my ball, you don't play at all: Russell Long
    I'm liberating: Sukarno, rubber plantations
    I'm not doing business with any non-capitalist: trade, AFL-CIO, Lyndon Johnson
    I'm not meetin' any outside agitators from the United States!: George Wallace, demonstrations, Alabama State Police
    I'm sorry, Mr. President, Major White just stepped out: space exploration
    In the meantime find me another revolution: Fidel Castro, Dominican Republic
    An Institution: Charles De Gaulle as the Eiffel Tower
    It's about time you shaped up!: draft
    It's harmless: peace, Israel, Abdel Gamal Nasser, Habib Bourguiba
    It says, calling this a war would cause complications: Vietnam War